{"showBridgeTasks":true,"taskHeader":"Pool Cover Services","categoryPerformanceTest":true,"scrollyPathPageBase":"","providedPostalCode":"","hideAllSemIcons":false,"__cache./api/resource/task/interview/46336/":{"taskOID":46336,"originalTaskOID":46336,"setID":1032,"interviewType":"TASK_INTERVIEW","questions":[{"questionID":200216,"questionDisplayText":"Purpose of Cover:","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What is the purpose of the pool cover? (Select all that apply)","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":17440,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Keep out children and pets","answerDisplayText":"Keep out children and pets","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":17441,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Replace fencing for code compliance","answerDisplayText":"Replace fencing for code compliance","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":17442,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Provide winter protection","answerDisplayText":"Provide winter protection","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":17443,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Protect pool while away","answerDisplayText":"Protect pool while away","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":17444,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Keep trash and leaves out of pool","answerDisplayText":"Keep trash and leaves out of pool","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":200215,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Cover Type:","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Select the type of swimming pool cover you are interested in:","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":17435,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Safety Cover","answerDisplayText":"Safety Cover","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":17436,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Automatic Cover","answerDisplayText":"Automatic Cover","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":17437,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Winter Cover","answerDisplayText":"Winter Cover","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":17438,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Insulated Cover","answerDisplayText":"Insulated Cover","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":17439,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Spa Cover","answerDisplayText":"Spa Cover","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":17149,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Would like recommendation","answerDisplayText":"Would like recommendation","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":200217,"questionDisplayText":"Type of Pool:","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What type of swimming pool would you like to cover?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11513,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Above ground","answerDisplayText":"Above ground","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11514,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"In ground","answerDisplayText":"In ground","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":7735,"questionDisplayText":"What kind of location is this?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":5,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"What kind of location is this?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":501504,"questionDisplayText":"Property Owner","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":7,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","shortQuestionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]}],"questionElements":[{"questionID":200216,"questionDisplayText":"Purpose of Cover:","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What is the purpose of the pool cover? (Select all that apply)","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":17440,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Keep out children and pets","answerDisplayText":"Keep out children and pets","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":17441,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Replace fencing for code compliance","answerDisplayText":"Replace fencing for code compliance","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":17442,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Provide winter protection","answerDisplayText":"Provide winter protection","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":17443,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Protect pool while away","answerDisplayText":"Protect pool while away","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":17444,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Keep trash and leaves out of pool","answerDisplayText":"Keep trash and leaves out of pool","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":17440,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Keep out children and pets","answerDisplayText":"Keep out children and pets","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":17441,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Replace fencing for code compliance","answerDisplayText":"Replace fencing for code compliance","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":17442,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Provide winter protection","answerDisplayText":"Provide winter protection","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":17443,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Protect pool while away","answerDisplayText":"Protect pool while away","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":17444,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Keep trash and leaves out of pool","answerDisplayText":"Keep trash and leaves out of pool","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":200215,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Cover Type:","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Select the type of swimming pool cover you are interested in:","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":17435,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Safety Cover","answerDisplayText":"Safety Cover","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":17436,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Automatic Cover","answerDisplayText":"Automatic Cover","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":17437,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Winter Cover","answerDisplayText":"Winter Cover","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":17438,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Insulated Cover","answerDisplayText":"Insulated Cover","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":17439,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Spa Cover","answerDisplayText":"Spa Cover","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":17149,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Would like recommendation","answerDisplayText":"Would like recommendation","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":17435,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Safety Cover","answerDisplayText":"Safety Cover","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":17436,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Automatic Cover","answerDisplayText":"Automatic Cover","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":17437,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Winter Cover","answerDisplayText":"Winter Cover","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":17438,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Insulated Cover","answerDisplayText":"Insulated Cover","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":17439,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Spa Cover","answerDisplayText":"Spa Cover","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":17149,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Would like recommendation","answerDisplayText":"Would like recommendation","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":200217,"questionDisplayText":"Type of Pool:","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What type of swimming pool would you like to cover?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11513,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Above ground","answerDisplayText":"Above ground","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11514,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"In ground","answerDisplayText":"In ground","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":11513,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Above ground","answerDisplayText":"Above ground","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11514,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"In ground","answerDisplayText":"In ground","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":7735,"questionDisplayText":"What kind of location is this?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":5,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"What kind of location is this?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":501504,"questionDisplayText":"Property Owner","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":7,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","shortQuestionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]}]},"scrolly_persistedParams":{},"addressId":null,"AdobeFlickerMgmtOn":false,"SCROLLY_FILTER_NON_REQUIRED_33367":false,"headerBranding":{"src":"/images/consumer/cobranding/HA.svg","name":"ha"},"entryPointId":0,"matchingSourceId":2,"scrollyProgressBarTest":false,"isMobile":false,"consumer":{"entityId":0},"affiliateCode":"sm_def_sto","twoPageSubmit":true,"sar":true,"scrolly_customDefaults":["50001_10002","8152_10002","30001_10002","160804_10002","20001_10002","160807_10002","160805_10002","502713_10002","160810_6938","8373_67562","8374_67566"],"entityId":0,"sessionId":"1564368210609pwspr010376737CC5AE756748174EA7F763C984D.pwspr010-1","shouldShowTasks":true,"__cache./api/resource/task/46336/?r_version=1":{"taskOid":46336,"taskName":"Swimming Pool Covers - Install or Replace","taskDescription":"Install or Replace Covers for a Swimming Pool","xmTaskDescriptor":"Pool Cover Services","matchable":false,"profileable":true,"esScore":0.0,"defaultCostGuideTaskId":184,"active":true,"taskKeywords":"swim swimming pool cover safety","textMessagingName":"Inst Pool Cover","rolloverLongDesc":"Includes manual \u0026 automatic covers made of netting, mesh, vinyl or other material","rolloverShortDesc":"Includes manual \u0026 automatic covers made of netting, mesh, vinyl or other material","sectorId":"HS","metaDescription":"Find local contractors to Install or Replace Covers for a Swimming Pool.  HomeAdvisor will connect you with prescreened and customer-rated contractors in your area","htmlTitle":"Pool Cover Installation \u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e | Replace Pool Cover","contentDescription":null,"pwcId":61,"acceptGoal":3,"multiZip":false,"preMatchTypeId":0,"bridgeTaskOid":0,"bridgeTaskText":null,"bridgeTaskLinkText":null,"bridgeTaskLinkId":0,"bridgeTaskActive":"N","xmName":"Swimming Pool Covers Install","redirectToTaskOid":-1,"spDisplayName":"Swimming Pool Covers - Install or Replace","xmHeaderDescriptor":"Describe Your Swimming Pool Cover Project","urlName":"Swimming-Pool-Covers-Install-or-Replace","taskConsiderationId":1,"siteVisible":true,"attributeMatchable":false,"htmlTitleTloc":"\u003cspcount\u003e Best Pool Cover Installation Services - \u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e | HomeAdvisor","searchKeywords":"swim,swimming,pool,cover,safety,netting,automatic","emcCategoryOid":-12070,"locationDisplayText":"What is the location of your project?","semLocationDisplayText":"To get started, enter the location of your project","commentsPromptText":"Please provide a short description of your project","primaryQuestionSetId":1032,"locationSpecific":false,"commercial":false,"viewFirstParentTask":false},"KNOWN_USER_SCROLLY_TEST_SITE_33390":"ctrl","semThreeIcons":false,"isCookielessUser":true}